{
  "topic": "6.1",
  "title": "Показательные уравнения",
  "types": [
    {
      "id": "6.1.1",
      "title": "",
      "prototypes": [
        {
          "id": "6.1.1.1",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\left(\\frac{1}{7}\\right)^{x+4} = 49 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -6 },
          "unic": true
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.1.2",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\left(\\frac{1}{3}\\right)^{x+2} = 27 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -5 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.1.3",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\left(\\frac{1}{2}\\right)^{x-1} = 16 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -3 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.1.4",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\left(\\frac{1}{5}\\right)^{x+1} = \\frac{1}{25} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 1 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.1.5",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 3^{x+1} = 27 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.1.6",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 5^{x-4} = 125 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 7 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.1.7",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 2^{x+3} = \\frac{1}{4} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -5 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.1.8",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 7^{2x-5} = 7 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 3 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.1.9",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\left(\\frac{1}{4}\\right)^{x+2} = \\frac{1}{64} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 1 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.1.10",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 9^{x+1} = 1 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -1 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.1.11",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 10^{x-1} = \\frac{1}{100} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -1 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.1.12",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\left(\\frac{1}{6}\\right)^{x-2} = 36 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 0 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.1.13",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 4^{2-x} = 16 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 0 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.1.14",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 3^{x-5} = \\frac{1}{9} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 3 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.1.15",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 8^{x+1} = 1 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -1 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.1.16",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\left(\\frac{1}{9}\\right)^{x} = 81 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.1.17",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 2^{4-x} = 32 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -1 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.1.18",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 5^{3-x} = \\frac{1}{25} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 5 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.1.19",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\left(\\frac{1}{8}\\right)^{x+3} = \\frac{1}{64} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -1 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.1.20",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 7^{x+2} = \\frac{1}{49} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -4 }
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "6.1.2",
      "title": "",
      "prototypes": [
        {
          "id": "6.1.2.1",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 2^{-4 - x} = 16 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -8 },
          "unic": true
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.2.2",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 3^{-x+1} = 27 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.2.3",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 5^{-x} = \\frac{1}{25} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.2.4",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 4^{-x-1} = \\frac{1}{16} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 1 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.2.5",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 2^{-x+3} = \\frac{1}{8} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 6 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.2.6",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 7^{-x+4} = 49 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.2.7",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 3^{-2-x} = \\frac{1}{9} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 0 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.2.8",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 2^{-x+1} = 32 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -4 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.2.9",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 5^{-x+2} = 125 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -1 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.2.10",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 3^{-x-3} = \\frac{1}{27} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 0 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.2.11",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 10^{-x+1} = \\frac{1}{10} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.2.12",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 2^{-x-2} = \\frac{1}{16} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.2.13",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 3^{2-x} = \\frac{1}{3} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 3 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.2.14",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 7^{1-x} = \\frac{1}{7} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.2.15",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 9^{3-x} = 81 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 1 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.2.16",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 4^{-x} = \\frac{1}{16} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.2.17",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 6^{-x+2} = \\frac{1}{36} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 4 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.2.18",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 8^{1-x} = 64 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -1 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.2.19",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 5^{-x+1} = \\frac{1}{5} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.2.20",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 2^{-x-1} = \\frac{1}{8} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 }
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "6.1.3",
      "title": "",
      "prototypes": [
        {
          "id": "6.1.3.1",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 3^{x+6} = 9^{2x} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 },
          "unic": true
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.3.2",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 2^{x+4} = 4^{x+1} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.3.3",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 5^{3x-4} = 25^{x-1} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.3.4",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 2^{2x+3} = 8^{x} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 3 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.3.5",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 7^{x+5} = 49^{x+1} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 3 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.3.6",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 9^{x} = 3^{x+1} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 1 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.3.7",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 4^{2x-1} = 2^{3x} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.3.8",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 25^{x+1} = 5^{3x+2} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 0 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.3.9",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 3^{x+2} = 9^{x} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.3.10",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 8^{2x+1} = 2^{5x-2} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -5 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.3.11",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 27^{x+1} = 3^{4x+1} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.3.12",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 16^{x} = 2^{3x+1} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 1 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.3.13",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 9^{2x-3} = 3^{3x-1} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 5 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.3.14",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 5^{3x-2} = 25^{x} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.3.15",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 7^{3x-2} = 49^{x} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.3.16",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 4^{x+3} = 8^{x-1} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 9 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.3.17",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 3^{4x-2} = 9^{x} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 1 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.3.18",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 2^{x+6} = 4^{2x} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.3.19",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 5^{x+4} = 25^{2x-1} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.1.3.20",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large 9^{x+2} = 27^{x} \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 4 }
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
